A.
Amy is learning about the craft of tie-dying and has found an article about it.
Read the article and answer the questions below.
Do you have a tie-dyed t-shirt?
Tie-dying is an old art with a history of over 1,500 years and it became most popular in the Tang dynasty.
Here are the steps for tie-dying.
First, twist a piece of cloth and tie it with string.
Then dye the material and when it is dry untie it.
The tied part stays the same colour as before but the rest has a different colour.
Today in some parts of Yunnan province, for example, local people still use traditional tie-dying methods to make different products like scarves and bags.
Tie-dying is not only a form of art but also a lifestyle.